https://www.medpharm.com/en/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyYour privacy is extremely important to us. Click here to read how MedPharm Ltd are taking steps to protect your personal data.Your Data Privacy MattersAt MedPharm, we use your personal data to provide our customers and website visitors (yes, you!) with the best service possible. We are very serious about your privacy and protecting your data, which is why we never unnecessarily collect your information. You can see more details below about the kind of data we collect and, more importantly, why we collect it.  We aren’t really making any changes to how we collect and process your data but in line with the new GDPR we just wanted to make sure that you are clear on what happens with your information. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy please contact us at dataprotection@medpharm.com. Who are we?MedPharm Ltd is the data controller of the data that we collect from you. This means that we decide the way in which we collect and process your personal data. We are registered as a company in England and Wales under company number 03783386 and our registered address is Unit 3, Chancellor Court 50 Occam Road, Surrey Research Park, Guildford, Surrey, GU2 7AB What information we collect about you and whyPersonal data can cover a wide variety of things. Thankfully at MedPharm we do not need to collect any highly sensitive personal data about you in order to work effectively with you.What data do we collect?How do we collect the data?Full name and contact information (email address, telephone number, company name & address, job titleWhen you send us an initial email When we meet you and exchange business cards When we find you through social media- e.g. LinkedIn When we receive conference attendee listsYour company bank detailsWe will only collect this information when you send it to usInformation about how you use our websiteData analytics tools using cookies. Learn more about how we use cookies on our website below.Information about how you interact with our marketing emailsWhen you open or click on any links in the marketing emails that we send youAll of our information is stored securely in our CRM system, Salesforce. Additionally, only select members of the MedPharm team have access to this information which helps us to protect your information even more. You can find out more about what specific things Salesforce are doing in order to protect your privacy at salesforce.com. How we use your personal dataWhat we use your personal data forWhy?Your payment information to take payment and give refundsWe’ve got to do this to fulfill our contract with youYour contact information is used in business communications.To ensure we are providing you with the best service we need to be able to contact you regarding new and ongoing projects.Information about how you surf our website is used to improve our website.We need this information to help us to improve the content on our website to ensure that you get the best experienceYour contact information is used to send marketing emailsThis is to keep you up to date with our news and services. You can opt out of this information at any time.Your responses to surveys and competitionsThe information helps us to improve our services. Also, we need to keep your data to have a way of letting you know that you have won!We will hold on to your personal data for as long as it is necessary to carry out the processes in this policy. This depends on what we are using the data for and how our holding this data impacts both you and MedPharm. We will never keep your data longer than necessary and will actively review the data we hold to ensure that it is still relevant. Transfer of your data outside the EEAThere may be times when we need to transfer your personal data outside the EEA (European Economic Area). For example, when we communicate with our US facility. However, if we do transfer your data in this way we will take steps, as set out in this privacy policy to ensure the safety and security of your personal data. What are your rights?As an individual you have a lot of rights relating to your personal data – it is yours after all!The right to be informed about how your personal data is being usedThe right to access the personal data that we hold on youThe right to request that we correct any inaccurate data that we hold on youThe right to request that we delete, restrict processing or collecting your data, in some circumstancesThe right to unsubscribe to direct marketing messages (you can do this at the bottom of any marketing emails that we send to you)The right to request the transfer elements of your personal data that we hold to you or another service provider of your choiceIf you have any queries or wish to exercise your rights, please contact us at dataprotection@medpharm.com. More details on other options for contacting us are listed below. Marketing messagesFrom time to time we will send you emails relating to our services and upcoming events. You can stop receiving these at any time by clicking the ‘unsubscribe’ link on any email. Alternatively you can contact us at dataprotection@medpharm.com to update your preferences. Once you do this, we will ensure that you no longer receive marketing emails. If you choose to do this you can always stay up to date with our latest news here and on LinkedIn. CookiesWe use cookies on our site to analyse and measure how our customers use the site. This helps us to improve our functionality and the content that we offer to you. The information that we collect from these cookies will not be disclosed outside of MedPharm Ltd or our authorised Third-Party Data Processors.By using our site, you agree to us placing these cookies on your device and accessing them whenever you visit. You can make changes to your cookie preferences at any time by accessing your browser settings. Changes to how we protect your privacyYou can always pop back to this page to find an up to date version of our Privacy Policy. We will only contact you about any major changes to save from filling up your inbox with minor updates. How to get in touchIt’s always great to hear from you, especially if you feel as though there are areas we need to improve- no one is perfect after all! Feel free to send an email through to dataprotection@medpharm.com or send us a letter to the following address:MedPharm Ltd, FAO Compliance Team, Unit 1 50 Occam Rd, Guildford, Surrey, GU2 7AB, UKv1.0 reviewed 23 Mar 2019Additional InfoPrivacy PolicyDisclaimerContact us
